you
picking wildflowers is a passion of mine
they are so abundant here that making a
little bouquet is a seasonal treat that
I look forward to all year you see I
live in a very rural part of Washington
state and the local wildflowers are
mostly undisturbed by humans I'm also
happy to say they're visited often by
the bees
I always try to be conscious when I
forage seeking the most abundant places
not picking more than a couple flowers
in one spot I ask for permission to take
bounty reassuring nature that I will
cherish her work and that she will not
have to share more than the smallest
portion
you
I think using this method is an
excellent philosophy for life consume
carefully and consciously and appreciate
the wonder and beauty of what you have
as humans we often take more than we
need not being able to imagine a life
where shopping and traveling isn't a
priority but it is possible and I find
that much satisfaction can come from it
that is my secret
I will see you guys next time consider
subscribing if you enjoyed this video
have a lovely day